(Penny:)Okay, help me out here.
How does an archeology professor
get that good with a whip?
(Howard:)Maybe he took a class
at the adult bookstore.
(Howard:)That's how I learned.
I can't believe you've never
seen Raiders of the Lost Ark.
And I can't believe you've
never read Eat, Pray, Love.
(Leonard:)When she comes out with
Eat, Pray, Run Away From A
Giant Boulder, I'll read it.
I don't care if Eat, Pray, Love
changed your life,
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)I'm not reading it.
(Penny:)You know, I could totally
rock a hat like that.
(Sheldon:)That's the work of noted
Hollywood costume designer
(Sheldon:)Deborah Nadoolman.
(Sheldon:)She also designed
(Sheldon:)the iconic red and black jacket
in Michael Jackson's
Thriller video,
(Sheldon:)which I've never viewed
in its entirety,
(Sheldon:)as I find zombies dancing
(Sheldon:)in choreographed synchronicity
implausible.